Guide to the Mount Vernon Seminary and College Mount Vernon Seminary and College graphics, publications, and administrative material collection, 1890-2000 MVC0035.MS
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Mount Vernon Seminary and College graphics, publications, and administrative material collection
1875-2002
1920-1997
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Mount Vernon College
Mount Vernon Seminary
MVC0035.MS
20 Linear Feet document boxes and oversized boxes
This collection contains photographs, slides, scrapbook pages, faculty handbooks, correspondence, brochures, event programs, student and alumni publications, and oversized poster boards and artifacts, which include plaques, framed photographs, Mount Vernon College themed paraphenalia, and various items of A/V equipment. These materials documenting the the daily lives of students, special college events, and alumni involvement in college life, were produced and used by students and faculty of the Mount Vernon Seminary and College between 1875 and 2002.
Scope and Content
This collection contains photographs, slides, scrapbook pages, faculty handbooks, correspondence, brochures, event programs, student and alumni publications, and oversized poster boards and artifacts, which include plaques, framed photographs, and Mount Vernon College themed paraphenalia. These materials were produced and used by students and faculty of the Mount Vernon Seminary and College, a private Washington, D.C. women's college which operated from 1875 until 1999, when it merged with the George Washington University. Items date from 1875 to 2002.
The majority of photographs and other visual materials in this collection document the daily lives and special activities of students, and were created either by the students themselves or by the institution for promotional purposes. Other photographs document a wide variety of alumni events; photo albums and scrapbook pages trace the lives of alumni from their student days to their shared reunions decades later. Images of the Mount Vernon campus range from informal snapshots of storm damage and students outdoors, to architectural drawings and posters showcasing the opening of new buildings. In addition to the large number of images, supplementary material including event programs, brochures, and publications give context to the photographs of theatre productions, student portraits, and campus scenes. A small number of administrative materials associated with the photographic material has also been included. The factbooks, chronologies, and correspondence in this administrative series provide an overview of college life and insight into some of the larger college events depicted in photographs.
Of special interest in this collection are scrapbook pages dating to the early half of the 20th century and created by students to reflect the highlights of their college experience. The class of 1940 photo album, in particular, shows the progression of a cohort of young women from graduation up to their 50th reunion, illuminating the continuing involvement of alumni and their dedication to the college. Finally, the oversized materials include a variety of class photos and plaques of dedication and celebration, revealing the community-centered character of the college and its students.
Restrictions on Access
This collection is open for research.
Acquisition Note
The Mount Vernon Seminary and College archives were acquired by GWU upon merger with Mount Vernon College. The collection was transferred to the Foggy Bottom campus in 2009.
Other Finding Aids
There are many collections from the Mount Vernon Archives that contains similar topics and types of content to that found within this collection. Please use http://library.gwu.edu/scrc/search/finding-aids-by-topic/mount-vernon-seminary-and-college for a complete list.
General
Boxes 27-29 and 30-39 were added to this collection at later dates. The materials are arranged within these boxes chronologically by series.
Arrangement
Organized into 9 series: Slides, Photographs, Scrapbook Pages, Administrative Materials, Brochures, Event Programs, Student and Alumni Publications, Artifacts, and Oversized Posters and Plaques.
Biographical/Historical Note
The Mount Vernon Seminary was officially established by Elizabeth Somers in 1875 with classes held at her residence on F Street; she named it after her brother's church in Baltimore, Mount Vernon Place Methodist. The Seminary began as a six year prepatory school, with four years of high school level classes, and two years of post-high school curriculum, calling it a "Family and Day School for Young Ladies." In order to graduate, students had to complete a formal process of "Senior Essays" in which they completed primary research and wrote on a current political or social topic, including such provocative issues as child labor, prohibition, poverty, and women's suffrage.
The school was moved to 1100 M. Street N.W. in 1900 and was once again moved in 1917 to a campus on Nebraska Avenue. In 1920 graduating class, eight women continued their education at universities such as the University of Wisconsin, Stanford, Northwestern and the University of Texas; by 1923 graduates were going to such other prestigious universities as UC-Berkeley, Columbia, Cornell, Smith College and the University of Chicago. Such advancements in higher education were uncommon for women of the day, but Mount Vernon was one of the premier prepatory institutions in the country.
In 1927, Mount Vernon established a Junior College, and with its establishment, students no longer had to complete six years of courses to receive a diploma; they graduated from the Seminary after four years and could continue on to the Junior College for two more years of college preparation. After World War II began, the U.S. Navy took over the campus in 1942 as a part of the war effort. During the 1943 academic year, the Seminary held classes in Spring Valley by leasing neighborhood residences. After receiving "just compensation" for their Nebraska Avneue campus, the school purchased 21 acres on Foxhall Road and surrounding areas in 1945, and had applied for accreditation to award Associates of Arts Degrees after completing two years of the Junior College.
Despite its expansion, by 1965 the Board of Trustees voted unanimously to dissolve the Seminary by 1969, as it could not financially support both institutions. During the 1960s, the Junior College developed new academic concentrations such as government, international relations and political science to reflect its location in the nation's capital. At the same time, it began to phase out its vocational training such as home economics and secretarial skills to make room for these higher education courses.
By 1973, the Board of Higher Education licensed the college to award Bachelor of Arts (BA) degrees such as Public Affairs, Government, Business Administration, Childhood, Special Education, and the Visual Arts, as well as honorary Doctor of Humane Letters and Juris Doctor Degrees; in 1976, the college received initial accreditation as a four-year college and was reaccredited ten years later. However, by 1996 the college announced a plan to affiliate with George Washington University and the last class of Mount Vernon College graduated in 1999. Today, as an affiliated campus of GWU, Mount Vernon offers special living accommodations, as well as learning and leadership programs for female students.
Women's colleges; Washington (D.C.) -- History; Students; Student activities; Schools -- Washington (D.C.); Programs; Photographs; Education, Higher -- United States; Post, Marjorie Merriweather; Kayser, Elmer Louis
- Slides, 1875-2000; 1970-1990; Series 1
  Arrangement Note
  Organized chronologically
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains color slides depicting images of student life, athletics, campus, and events like commencement, field trips, and other celebratory activities. In addition to these images of student life, a large number of slides created by students to document pollution in the Washington area are of particular interest. A small handful slides used by faculty in the classroom are also represented. The bulk of the material dates from the 1970's to the 1990's.
  - Historic shots, Circa 1875-1950; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Commencement and Founder's Day circa 1958, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Campus - Winter Scenes, 1967-1981; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Campus - Fall Scenes, 1969-1981; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - America the Beautiful? Earth Day 1970, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Environment and Pollution in DC - Mary Heller, Cindy Ratsey, Maurice and Pamela Mountain, 1970; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Commencement 1970-1974, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Student Life 1970-1979 [1/3], Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Student Life 1970-1979 [2/3], Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Student Life 1970-1979 [3/3], Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Students - Sports, 1970-1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - History and Art - World Wars, 1971-1975; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Students - Groups in Class, 1971-1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Students - Relaxing, 1971-1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Horseback Riding, 1972-1973; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Students - Europe Trip, 1972-1979; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Students - In Art Class, 1972-1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Students - Individuals in Class, 1972-1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Students - in Georgetown, 1972-1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Students - Walking, 1972-1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Students - Working at Office, 1972-1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Washington Institutions, 1972-1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Students - Special Activities, 1973-1979; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Students - Walking (Face Shots), 1973-1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Student & Faculty Communication, 1974-1979; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Faculty, 1976-1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Optical Illusions, 1976-1982; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Students - Field Trip, 1977-1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Students - Housing, 1977-1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Campus - Library, Labs & Media, 1978-1979; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Campus - Summer Scenes, 1978-1981; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Italy 1979, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Arts and Humanities Majors, 1979-1981; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Campus Scenes 1979-1981, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Campus - Tennis Court, 1979-1981; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Students & Faculty in the Classroom, 1979-1981; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Communication, 1979-1983; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder data_value_missing_f6b9015e89d3dd98d468ac46dece6c3e)
  - Interior Design Students, 1979-1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Student Life Undated (Circa 1980's), Series 1 (Box 3, Folder data_value_missing_b4b5e7cfa31dd9ac883095c0b74a75dd)
  - Students on campus, Circa 1980s; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Commencement 1981, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Student Life 1981, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Washington Scenes with Students, 1981-1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Sports 1981-1989, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Gatehouse Garally, 1982; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Post Hall, 1982; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Commencement 1983, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Dona Daniel; Jean Freeman, Assistant Professor of Interior Design, 1983; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Judy Grogan, Pat Balan (Associate Professor, Economics), Shannon Porter, 1983; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Mildred Lamm, Chair, Interior Design Program, 1983; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Office Scenes, 1983; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Politics, 1983; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Robert Kaplan, chair, communications program, 1983; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Student Life 1983, Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Student on campus (slides by William Denison), 1983; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Student Portraits 1983, Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Sue Bredekamp, adjunct, professor of human development, w/ May Thomasson, 1983; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Campus Scenes 1983-1989 [1/2], Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Campus Scenes 1983-1989 [2/2], Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Life, ca. 1983-1990; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Commencement 1985, Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Student Life 1985-1986, Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 1986 Baccalaureate/Alum Reception, Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Baccalaureate & Commencement 1986, Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Business Still Life, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 1986 Coffee Concert, Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Coffee/Dessert at Dr. Evans' House with Students, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Dean Donna Carroll & Student Kim Saffery 1986, Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Debra Terri Internship - Bartender's Association, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Brintnall Classroom shots, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Inaugural Ball Invite w/ Corsage, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Janet Raimondo and Gail Timmerman - Successful Alumnae Shot, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Janet Thompson - Aerobics Student, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Kelly Gioia, Debra Ferri, Laura Kinney, Tammy Adams - Students/Men at Post Office Pavilion, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Kelly Gioia, Tammy Adams, Laura Kinney - Students shopping in Georgetown, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Kelly Gioia & Tammy Adams - National Gallery of Art, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Kendall Hall Search Piece Cover Shots, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Laura Kinney CIS6 WTLA - TV Internship, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Library Groundbreaking 1986, Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Linette Rapp Student Teaching at Key School, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Pub Night - Men & Students, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Regina Chung - Student, Wall Street Journal, Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Science Still Life, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Snow - Students & Campus 1986, Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Spring Cherry Blossoms w/ Student Wendy Stiles, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Student Caroline Barco at Capitol Building, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Students - Clark Dorm, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Tennis Still Life, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Wendy Stiles - Student Career Planning, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Campus Buildings, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Events & Commencement, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Events & Commencement 1987-1988, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Student Life 1987-1988 [1/2], Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Student Life 1987-1988 [2/2], Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Tennis 1987-1988, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Students on campus (slides by Bill Burke), Circa late 1980s - early 1990s; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Students and campus (slides by Richard Basch), Circa late 1980s - early 1990s; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Beacon Honor Society & Library Skylight Spring 1988, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Christmas Tree, 12 Dec 1988, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Founder's Day, 14 Nov 1988, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Seminar/ NWMA, 29 Nov 1988, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - GLIMPSE/'86 Alums in PUB, 11 Oct 1988, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Interior Design Decorates for OEB Christmas Party, 1988; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Orientation Groups, 21 Jul 1988, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - SGA Tree Trimming, 6 Dec 1988, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Students on campus (slides by Richard T. Nowitz), Circa 1989 - 1990; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Mount Vernon campus, Circa 1990s; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Students and faculty on campus (slides by Bill Denison) [1 of 2], 1990; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Students and faculty on campus (slides by Bill Denison) [2 of 2], 1990; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Students on campus (slides by Doug Barber), Circa 1990; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Students on campus (slides by P. Finger), 1990; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Student Life 1990-1992, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Student Life 1997-1998, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Campus Scenes 2000, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Undetermined Class Slides, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Photographs, 1875-2002; 1880-1999; Series 2
  Organized alphabetically by subject into 8 subseries: Athletics, Campus, Commencement, Events, Faculty, Students, Photo Albums and Oversized Photos.
  This series contains photographs and negatives documenting campus athletics, commencements activities, the Mount Vernon campus, various school events, faculty, and students. Many of these photos were taken for publicity purposes and are featured in the Mount Vernon alumni bulletin - others were taken by students themselves and represent personal photo albums and yearbook photo compilations. The material dates to between 1875 and 2002.
  - Athletics, 1920-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1
    - Students swimming in the pool, Circa 1920; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Student athletics on campus, Circa 1930s; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Student athletics, Circa 1940s; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Athletics 1960-1965, Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Athletics 1980-1989, Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Athletics 1990-1999, Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Athletics Undated, ca. 1970-1980; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Campus, 1880-2002; 1940-1999; Series 2 Subseries 2
    - Music room at 1100 M Street campus (Augustus Eddy with dog, "Gippo"), Circa 1880-1900; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Girls' bedroom, Circa 1940s; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Campus 1940-1949, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 4000 and 4020 Fordham (Spring Valley campus), Circa 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - "New Gatesley" at 3301 University Ave. (Spring Valley campus), Circa 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Campus 1950-1959, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Campus 1970-1979, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Campus 1980-1989, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Campus 1990-1999, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Campus improvements, Fall 1999; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Dorothy Williamson Clock Tower, Fall 2002; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Campus Undated, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Luca Della Robbia Lunette, Undated, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Commencement, 1930-2000; 1980-1999; Series 2 Subseries 3
    - Students on graduation day, Circa 1930s; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Commencement 1950-1959, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Commencement 1960-1969, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Commencement 1970-1979, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Commencement 1980-1989, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Commencement 1985 w/ Bonner, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Convocation 1988, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Commencement 1989 (contact sheets), Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Commencement 1990-1999, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Commencement 1993, 8 May 1993; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Commencement 1994, Spring 1994; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Convocation 1998, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Commencement and Baccalaureate 1999, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Students at Commencement, Circa 2000; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Commencement Undated, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Events, 1940-2000; 1980-1999; Series 2 Subseries 4
    - Events 1940-1949, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Events 1950-1959, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - May Day 1957, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Miss Ames Alumni Visit 1959, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Events 1960-1969, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - George and Olwen Lloyd at Founder's Day 1961, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Prep Players performance of "Peter Pan" (Foxhall Road campus), 1962; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Dr. Elmer Kayser at Convocation 1964, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Events 1970-1979, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Pearl Bailey Benefit 26 May 1977, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Victoria Schuck - Inauguration and Student Interaction, 1978; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Events 1980-1989, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - President Jane Evans at Events, 1980-1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Events circa late 1980's to early 1990's, 1985-1995; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Alumni Reunion 1982, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Eleanor Lansing Dulles and Student Trustee Andrea Leithoff, 1983; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Palm Beach Reception 1983, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Houston Junior League 1988, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Oklahoma City Alumni Network 1988, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Richmond, VA Alumni Reception 1988, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Founders Day 1989 (contact sheets), Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Springfest 1989, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Eleanor Phillips Colt, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Colloquy with Mrs. Kuryiama, Circa 1990s; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Events 1990-1999, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Women in Politics - Hand Chapel (negatives), Circa 1990s; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Bulletin Photographs 1992-1993, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Mrs. Kuryiama at Lucy Ann Geiselman's house, Circa 1992-1996; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - DC Happy Hour Around the Country 1993, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Reunion 1993, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Beacon Honor Society, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Founders Day 1994, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Women in Politics luncheon, Fall 1994; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Founders Day 1995, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Mount Vernon Tennis Classic 1995, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous event photos, Circa 1995-1999; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Abby Moffat and tea for Class of 1996, 3 March 1996; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - GWU signing, 1996; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Mount Vernon Tennis Classic 1996, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Women in Politics luncheon, 1996; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Mount Vernon Tennis Classic, Circa 1997; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Women in Politics and Journalism luncheon, 1997; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Family Weekend, Fall 1998; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Founders Day 1998, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Holiday party, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Mount Vernon Tennis Classic 1998, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Winter Formal 1998, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Pat Schroeder Leadership Speaker Series, Fall 1998; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 1)